Guide to the Alice Kleberg Reynolds papers, 1979-2004
Reynolds, Alice Kleberg papers, 1979-2004
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Alice Kleberg Reynolds papers, 1979-2004
7606
Alice Kleberg Reynolds
4.8 cubic feet
Subject files, ephemera.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Professional and personal subject files pertaining chiefly to the Human Rights Campaign Fund, and its work in AIDS education, advocacy, queer politics, women's rights campaigns, and gay and lesbian social and political issues.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Professional and personal subject files pertaining chiefly to the Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF), and its work in AIDS education, advocacy, queer politics, women's rights campaigns, and gay and lesbian social and political issues; includes queer ephemera, t-shirts, and buttons, as well as posters from HRCF and Texas political events, such as "Texas March to Stop the Violence, Stop the Hate" and a poster criticizing Senator Kay Bailey Hutchison. One large poster "Save the Amazons: Fight Breast Cancer," has "lesbian librarians" penciled at the bottom. Also, national posters from the 1993 March on Washington for Lesbian, Gay, and Bi Equal Rights and Liberation and other events. Includes publicity materials for San Antionio Black Tie dinners in 1995 and 1997, events that raised money for HRCF and local agencies.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Reynolds, Alice Kleberg.; Human Rights Campaign Fund.
Subjects:
Gays--Political activity.; Lesbians--Political activity.; AIDS (Disease)--Education.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Human Rights Campaign Fund
Boxes 1-2, 4-5, 10
Series II. Subject Files
Boxes 5-6
Series III. Ephemera
Boxes 3-4, 7-9, oversize folder
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Human Rights Campaign Fund
  - Action Network, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AIDS, 1988-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Americans Against Discrimination (AAD), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board Lists, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board By-Laws and Duties, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Civil Rights Bill Legislative, 1988-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Clinton, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
  - Colorado Amendment #2, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Development Committee, 1988-1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Education Bills, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1994 Elections, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 2000 Elections (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Endowment/Estate Planning, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
  - Event Mailings, 1988-1996 (Box 1, Folder 17-20)
  - Federal Advocacy Network, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Federal Club, 1989-1995 (Box 1, Folder 22-23)
  - Hate Crimes, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Healthcare, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Staff, Job Descriptions, Press Releases, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
  - Job Discrimination, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 28-30)
  - Congressional Employment Non-Discrimination Project, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Randy Klose Gay and Lesbian Leadership Conference, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Leadership Conferences, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Lesbians, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Maine #1 State Initiatives, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Marketing Materials, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Gay Marriage, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Military "Media", 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 38-39)
  - Campaign for Military Service, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 40-41)
  - Mission Goals, 1989-1995 (Box 1, Folder 42-43)
  - National Coming Out Day (NCOD), 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Newsletters, 1989-1994 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Political Action Committee, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Position Statements, 1989-1995 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Press Clippings, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Publications, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Senate/House Votes on Queer Politics, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Speak Out, 1991-1996 (Box 1, Folder 51-53)
  - Texas-San Antonio/Austin Events, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Voting Guide, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner: "Blazing a Trail", 1989 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner: "As Right As Rain", 1990 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner: "And the Beat Goes On", 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1-7)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner: "Casino Night", 1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner: "Creating a More Perfect Union", 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner: "Family Reunion", 1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner: "Working Out Together", 1995 (Box 2, Folder 11-15)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner: "Out Vote '96; We've Got the Power", 1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner: "Out On the Town", 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17-18)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner: Service Application, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - All Part of the Family Black Tie Dinner, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Many Voices One Vision Black Tie Dinner, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Freedom Black Tie Dinner, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Stand Out Black Tie Dinner, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Over The Rainbow Black Tie Dinner, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - A Time for Us Black Tie Dinner, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - We the People Black Tie Dinner, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - The Pursuit of Freedom Houston Black Tie Dinner, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Architects of Our Future Chicago Dinner and Dance, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Equal Rights For All Black Tie Dinner, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Meeting of the Board of Directors/Governors (February), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Meeting of the Board of Directors/Governors (September), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Meeting of the Board of Directors/Governers (February), 1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Meeting of the Board of Directors/Governors (August), 1994 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Meeting of the Board of Directors/Governors (November), 1994 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Joint Board of Directors and Board of Governors Meeting (September), 1995 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Executive Director Reports, Board of Governors Minutes and Reports, 1991-1995 (Box 2, Folder 36-37)
  - Executive Director Reports, Board of Governors Minutes and Reports, 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner poster and program proofs, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner newsletter proofs, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - HRCF event files, 1990-1997 (Box 10)
- Series II. Subject Files
  - Action Wisconsin, 1993-2003 (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
  - AIDS: Money Raising, 1990-1999 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Services: Miracle House, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Architecture Foundation Advisory Council, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Queer Archives, 1990-1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Lesbian Art, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Brochures, 1991-2003 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Queer Business: Mailorder, 1990-1996 (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
  - Human Rights Business: Shocking Gray, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 13-15)
  - Campaigns: Congress Tom Hecht, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Christian Coalition, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Concerned Women for America (CWA), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Conference: Women and Technology, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Conference Announcements, 1987-2000 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cornell and Ithaca Newsletters, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1982-2004 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Queer Culture Arts, 1982-2004 (Box 5, Folder 23-24)
  - Queer Curriculum, 1993-1999 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Dyke TV, 1992-1997 (Box 5, Folder 26-28)
  - Esperanza, 1995-2002 (Box 5, Folder 29-31)
  - Queer Foundations, 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Gay and Lesbian Community Center of San Antonio, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Queer Health, 1991-2001 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Queer Law, 1993-2003 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Queer Law: Lambda Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Lesbian/Gay Rights Lobby of Texas (LGRL), 1989-1997 (Box 5, Folder 37-40)
  - Queer March, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Lesbian and Gay Media Watch Group, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (NGLTF), 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - People for American Way, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Physician For Human Rights, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Choice Politics: National Abortion and Reproductive Rights Action League (NARAL), 1992-2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Choice Politics: Texas Abortion and Reproductive Rights Action League (TARAL), 1992-1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Gay Politics, 1992-1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Queer Politics: Roberta Achtenberg, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Queer Politics: Candidates, 1994-2003 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Gingrich, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Queer Politics: Senate Race Texas-Hutchinson/Krueger, 1993-1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - San Antonio Equal Rights Political Caucus (SAERPC), 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - San Antonio Lesbian and Gay Assembly (SALGA), 1991-1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - San Antonio Lesbian/Gay Political Caucus (SALGPC), 1993-1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Servicemembers Legal Defense Network (SLDN), 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Queer Sports, 1994-1999 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Female Spirituality: Goddess, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Queer Survays/Polls, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Texas Human Rights Foundation (THRF), 1989-1995 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Texas Freedom Alliance/Network, 1995-1999 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Texas Lesbian Conference, 1992-2004 (Box 6, Folder 19-21)
  - Gay Travel, 1992-1997 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - The United, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - United Our Way, 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Victory Fund, 1992-1999 (Box 6, Folder 25-26)
  - University of Wisconsin Queer Students, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Women's Organizations, 1992-2002 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Women's Organizations: Leadership Texas, 1985-1995 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Women's Organizations: National Organization for Women (NOW), 1977-1999 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Women's Organizations: Texas Foundation for Women's Resources, 1981-1987 (Box 6, Folder 31-32)
  - Women's Organizations: Women's Political Caucus (WPC), 1991-1999 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Womyn Lesbian Organizations: Legacy Fund, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Series III. Ephemera
  - T-shirts, buttons, etc. (Box 3)
  - Posters (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Posters, Includes some HRC-related items (Folder 1)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner T-Shirts, 1994-1997 (Box 7)
  - San Antionio Black Tie Dinner Drink Cozies, 1995-1999 (Box 7)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner Tokens, 1990 (Box 7)
  - San Antonio Black Tie Dinner Nametag, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Paper Decoration (Box 7)
  - Various buttons and pins (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
  - Stickers and Magnets (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - U-Matic Videotape: "Come Out Voting" Public Service Announcement (Box 6)
  - Videotapes: Human Rrights Campaign Fund, Birch at Josephine Street (Box 9)
  - Videotape: "Come Out Voting" Public Service Announcement (Box 9)
  - Videotape: Political Asylum Project of Austin, "Stories of Immigrant Survivors of Abuse: Remedies Under the Violence Against Women Act" (Box 9)
  - Videotapes: National Center for Lesbian Rights 25th Anniversary Gala; Highlights of 25 Years of Legal Advocacy, 2002 (Box 9)
  - Videotapes: Dyke TV, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Publications Removed From Collection 7606 - Cataloged As Serials In The Human Sexuality Collection:
10 Percent, San Francisco, CA. 2 issues.
1998 Capital Gains and Losses: A State by State Review of Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, Transgender, and HIV/AIDS-Related Legislation in 1998. Washington, D.C.: NGLTF Policy Institute, 1998.
Advocate, Los Angeles, CA. 3 issues.
Aspen Gay Ski Week Program, Aspen, CO. 1 issue.
Atlanta Community Yellow Pages, Atlanta, GA. 1997; 1999-2000.
Bailey, Robert W. Out & Voting: The Gay, Lesbian and Bisexual Vote in Congressional House Elections, 1990-1996. Washington, D.C.: NGLTF Policy Institute, 1998.
Baltimore Gay Paper, Baltimore, MD. 1 issue.
Bay Area Reporter, San Francisco, CA. 2 issues.
Blueboy, New York, NY. 1 issue.
Boston Phoenix, Boston, MA. Supplement: "One in Ten: A queer students' guide to the best homo hangouts in Boston." Sept. 1996.
Damron Women's Traveller, 1998.
Ellas Dicen, San Antonio, TX. 3 issues.
ETC, Atlanta, GA. 3 issues.
Eurogames 2004, Munich.
Feminist Majority Report, Artlington, VA. 2 issues.
Gay Chicago Magazine, Chicago, IL. 1 issue.
Gayellow Pages: The National Edition: USA & Canada for Gay Women & Men, New York, NY, 1991.
H Inc., Denver, CO. 1 issue.
Houston Voice, Houston, TX. 4 issues.
HRC Quarterly, Washington, DC. 10 issues.
Khan, Surina. Calculated Compassion: How the Ex-Gay Movement Serves the Right's Attack on Democracy. Published by Political Research Associates, The Policy Institute of the National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, and Equal Partners in Faith, 1998.
Ladyslipper Catalog: Music by Women & More, Durham, NC. 1 issue.
Legacy, New York, NY. issues.
Lesbian Alliance of Metro Milwaukee, Milwaukee, WI. 6 issues.
Lesbian News, Torrance, CA. 1 issue.
National Queer Arts Festival 2003, San Francisco, CA.
National Women's Polictical Caucus, Women's Political Times, Washington, D.C. 2 issues.
Olivia Cruises & Resorts: Vacations for Women, Oakland, CA. 8 issues and several inserts.
Out, North Hollywood, CA. 6 issues.
OutFront Colorado, Denver, CO. 1 issue.
Outlook, Columbus, OH. 1 issue.
OutSmart, Houston, TX. 3 issues.
Passport, San Francisco, CA. 1 issue.
People for the American Way, Hostile Climate, Washington, DC. 1995, 1997.
Pride '03, San Francisco, CA. 1 issue.
Quest Magazine, Denver, CO. 1 issue.
San Antonio Community News,, San Antonio, TX. 1 issue.
San Antonio Current, San Antonio, TX. 3 issues.
San Antonio Marquise, San Antonio, TX. 12 issues.
San Antonio Unity Yellow Pages, San Antonio, TX. 1 issue.
SapphFire, Austin, TX. 2 issues.
Southern Voice, Atlanta, GA. 2 issues.
The Stateswoman, Madison, WI. 1 issue.
Storyletters, San Antonio, TX. 6 issues.
Texas Triangle, Austin, TX. 215 issues.
Texas Women's Political Times, Austin, TX. 1 issue.
This Week in Texas, Houston, TX. 1 issue.
Travel News from Remote Possibilities, Wailuku, HI. 1 issue.
Unity, Madison, WI. 1 issue.
La Voz de Esperanza, San Antonio, TX. 5 issues and Special 10-Year Booklet.
Wolfe Video, New Almaden, CA. 1 issue.
WomanSpace, San Antonio, TX. 33 issues.
Women's Community Cancer Project, Cambridge, MA. 2 issues.
Zebra'z, San Antonio, TX. 1 issue.